easyclicktravel.com 2017-06-09

# Easy Click Travel - Privacy Policy

**Introduction**   
This privacy policy applies to [www.easyclicktravel.com](http://www.easyclicktravel.com/) owned and operated by Travel Holdings, Inc. This privacy policy describes how Travel Holdings, Inc. is committed to maintain security and confidentiality of the personal information gathered and used on the www.easyclicktravel.com website (“hereinafter the Website”). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information, 

easyclicktravel.com and its authorized technology, marketing and service providers may gather, store, and process personal information from the Website. 

**Information Collected**   
easyclicktravel.com collects information that you voluntarily provide to us on the Website. The types of personal identifying information (“PII”) that may be collected on the Website are customer name, names of companion travelers, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone number(s), date of birth, passport information, credit card and payment information, and weight. Non-personal data that you voluntarily provide to us may be collected onthe Website during your usage of the site. 

Children and individuals under 18 years of age are not permitted to register or make purchases on our site. 

**Collection of 3rd party PII**   
You may also provide personal information about other people, such as their name, date of birth and gender. This information is only used for the sole purpose of completing your request or for whatever reason it may have been provided. 

**Information Use**   
easyclicktravel.com gathers, stores, and processes the PII in order to respond to requests for travel products and services and to improve our Website and service. easyclicktravel.com will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy and may share your information with its authorized technology, marketing and service providers. However, easyclicktravel.com does not sell, share, rent, or trade personal information to third parties for promotional purposes. The suppliers of travel inventory (hotels, cruise lines, etc.) that receive your information may have privacy policies that are differentthan this Privacy Policy. Our credit card processing uses your PII solely to facilitate the completion of your travel booking. 

**Tracking Technologies**   
Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Travel Holdings, Inc. and our partners [specify type e.g. marketing partners], affiliates, or analytics or service providers [specify type e.g. online customer support provider, etc]. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

We use cookies for [our shopping cart, to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference), for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. 

**Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting**   
We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. 

**Log Files**  
Non-personal information may be linked to your PII and provided to authorized, third parties to improve our Website and service. These third parties may be located outside the USA. 

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data [We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you] – OR – [We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this [to improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality.] 

**Local Storage Objects (HTML5)**   
We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 to store [content information and preferences.] Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. PII that you voluntarily provide to easyclicktravel.com when you register with us can be edited or removed by accessing the Member section on our Website by logging into “My Account” and changing your personal information. We may retain travel records for six (6) months after a request for removal to ensure that the any existing travel arrangements are concluded and/or if we are legally required to retain the records. If you provide easyclicktravel.com with additional PII, such as travel provider membership numbers or ticketing preferences, we may retain that information. This information may be edited or removed, as well. You may not be able to edit or remove data or information we collect from third parties. You can also send an email to [webmaster@travelholdings.com](mailto:webmaster@travelholdings.com) to have your PII changed. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes, and to enforce our agreements. 

**Communications from the Site and How to Opt-out**   
You will receive transaction or service related communications from the Website when you purchase travel products and services through our Website. Additionally, you will receive promotional communications from us if you choose to receive these communications. 

You may choose at any time during the registration process to “opt-out” and choose not to receive promotional communications that easyclicktravel.com feels may interest you. You may choose to unsubscribe and not receive future promotional communications by accessing the unsubscribe link on an email received by easyclicktravel.com. You can also “opt-out” of receiving these newsletters by logging into your account and “opting-out” of receiving these newsletters. 

**Tell-A-Friend**   
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. easyclicktravel.com does not store this information. 

**Blogs and Testimonials**   
If you comment to a blog or post a testimonial on this Website, you should be aware that any PII you submit can be read, collected, or used by other users on these forums, and the PII can be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for and will not protect the privacy of the PII you choose to submit in these forums. 

**Service Providers**   
We use third parties to provide credit card processing, email services, web-analytics, and live-chat services on our Website. When you sign up for these services, we will share your PII as necessary for the third party to provide the services. These third parties are prohibited from using your PII for any other purpose. We also have Widgets on this Website which support functions that require that you to disclose certain PII depending on your choice of participation. This information is collected in many different ways such as: forms, surveys, contests, forums, subscribing or unsubscribing to mailings and correcting or updating personal information and are only used for the purpose in which they were collected. 

**Security and Confidentiality**   
The security of your PII is important to us. When you enter sensitive information such as credit card number on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the PII submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your PII, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

When you click on any links on our Website, you leave our Website and enter the website of a third party. Your visit to these third party websites are governed by the privacy and security policies, if any, of those third party sites. easyclicktravel.com is not responsible for security and confidentiality of your information on third party sites. 

We reserve the right to disclose your PII as required by law, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. In addition, easyclicktravel.com may disclose certain information in cases of fraud or abuse of the Website. If Travel Holdings, Inc. in involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regardingyour personal information. 

**Social Media Widgets**   
Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, whichpage you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions withthese Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

**Single Sign-On**   
You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us suchas your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network. 

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**   
Changes to this Privacy Policy may be made from time to time. If any change is unacceptable to you, you may edit or remove your information subject to the restrictions noted herein and/or change your opt-out preference. easyclicktravel.com will either inform you by email if you have registered on our Website or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective, or another place we deem appropriate, of any material change to this Privacy Policy so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. 

**Contact Us**   
If you would like to contact us regarding this Privacy Policy, you can reach us by our mailing address at 220 East Central Parkway, Suite 4000, Altamonte Springs, FL 32701 or by email at [webmaster@travelholdings.com](mailto:webmaster@travelholdings.com).
